[
  {
    "front": "brillant, remarquable, Angleterre",
    "back": "英"
  },
  {
    "front": "argent",
    "back": "銀"
  },
  {
    "front": "(préfixe)",
    "back": "院"
  },
  {
    "front": "fois, degré",
    "back": "度"
  },
  {
    "front": "paix, tranquilité, bon marché",
    "back": "安"
  },
  {
    "front": "cœur esprit",
    "back": "心"
  },
  {
    "front": "lourd, important, grave, superposer",
    "back": "重"
  },
  {
    "front": "génération, âge, prix, représenter, remplacer, génération",
    "back": "代"
  },
  {
    "front": "Han (dynastie), Chine, homme",
    "back": "漢"
  },
  {
    "front": "vêtements, habillement, dose",
    "back": "服"
  }
]
